<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Progress Reports on Arjun Iyer</title>
    <link>https://arjun-i.github.io/ALL-FSLResearch/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Progress Reports on Arjun Iyer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://arjun-i.github.io/ALL-FSLResearch/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>November 3, 2021</title>
      <link>https://arjun-i.github.io/ALL-FSLResearch/post/post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arjun-i.github.io/ALL-FSLResearch/post/post4/</guid>
      <description>I have created a Digital Research Portfolio using Hugo and Github pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 3, 2021 - November 17, 2021</title>
      <link>https://arjun-i.github.io/ALL-FSLResearch/post/post5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arjun-i.github.io/ALL-FSLResearch/post/post5/</guid>
      <description>11/10/21:
New resource found on Kaggle for Building siamese networks: https://www.kaggle.com/krishnaprasad96/siamese-network/notebook
We will first try to find already existing weights for a ResNet50 model to input into ImageNet.
We discovered that ResNet can be used for the purposes of Siamese Networks, but more research needs to be done in order to understand the usages of it for the purposes of our Research Project.
(Most past research has used ReLU as the activation function for all outputs, which we are currently looking at using for the purposes of our project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2021</title>
      <link>https://arjun-i.github.io/ALL-FSLResearch/post/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arjun-i.github.io/ALL-FSLResearch/post/post2/</guid>
      <description>We have recently come into contact with two researchers at Genentech, who have assisted us regarding this project. We plan on having more future meetings with these researchers, which will take place sometime soon. More information about these meetings can be found in the Scientist Meetings section of this portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 28, 2021</title>
      <link>https://arjun-i.github.io/ALL-FSLResearch/post/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arjun-i.github.io/ALL-FSLResearch/post/post1/</guid>
      <description>I have set up a Collab Pro account, which I plan on using for its Cloud GPU and TPU capabilities which make is very useful for the purposes of machine learning. We plan on starting our model creation process very soon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
